[
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "C/C++ , Python , Tensorflow , Scikit learn , RAG",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "C/C++ , Python , Tensorflow , Scikit learn , RAG",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , Tensorflow , c/c++ , scikit learn , sql",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , Tensorflow , c/c++ , scikit learn , sql",
    "responses": [
      {
        "question": "Describe the tradeoffs between using TensorFlow and scikit-learn for a large-scale machine learning project involving image classification.",
        "answer": "Neural network and easy ML"
      },
      {
        "question": "Explain how you would optimize a computationally expensive TensorFlow model for deployment on a resource-constrained embedded system using C/C++.",
        "answer": "askdKAD"
      },
      {
        "question": "Design a system using Python, SQL, and TensorFlow to ingest, process, and analyze a large stream of sensor data for anomaly detection, outlining your choices for database schema and model architecture.",
        "answer": "SADJADADJ"
      },
      {
        "question": "How would you debug a memory leak in a C++ application that interacts with a TensorFlow model through a Python wrapper?",
        "answer": "asmn asjfjaqlaw"
      },
      {
        "question": "Compare and contrast the use of different regularization techniques in scikit-learn and how their effectiveness might vary across different datasets and model types.",
        "answer": "ans alajdadjkd"
      }
    ],
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , Tensorflow , c/c++ , scikit learn , sql",
    "responses": [
      {
        "question": "Describe the tradeoffs between using TensorFlow and scikit-learn for a large-scale machine learning project involving image classification.",
        "answer": "Neural network and easy ML"
      },
      {
        "question": "Explain how you would optimize a computationally expensive TensorFlow model for deployment on a resource-constrained embedded system using C/C++.",
        "answer": "askdKAD"
      },
      {
        "question": "Design a system using Python, SQL, and TensorFlow to ingest, process, and analyze a large stream of sensor data for anomaly detection, outlining your choices for database schema and model architecture.",
        "answer": "SADJADADJ"
      },
      {
        "question": "How would you debug a memory leak in a C++ application that interacts with a TensorFlow model through a Python wrapper?",
        "answer": "asmn asjfjaqlaw"
      },
      {
        "question": "Compare and contrast the use of different regularization techniques in scikit-learn and how their effectiveness might vary across different datasets and model types.",
        "answer": "ans alajdadjkd"
      }
    ],
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 0,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , C , ML",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 0,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , C , ML",
    "responses": [],
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , c/c++ , tensorflow , git",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Python , c/c++ , tensorflow , git",
    "responses": [
      {
        "question": "Describe a scenario where using C++ over Python would be significantly beneficial for a machine learning project, and justify your choice.",
        "answer": "jvhllb"
      },
      {
        "question": "Explain how you would debug a memory leak in a C++ program interacting with TensorFlow.",
        "answer": "bjzhckzcvkjz"
      },
      {
        "question": "Design a system for version controlling a large TensorFlow model, considering factors like model size, experiment tracking, and collaborative development using Git.",
        "answer": "scn c kfaA"
      },
      {
        "question": "Discuss the trade-offs between using eager execution and graph execution in TensorFlow, providing examples where one approach is preferable.",
        "answer": "nj;bhvvgvv"
      },
      {
        "question": "How would you optimize a computationally expensive TensorFlow model for inference on a resource-constrained device?",
        "answer": "jkxczvn;GZ"
      }
    ],
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 4,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , Tensorflow , Deep Learning , scikit learn , git",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T09:33:48.024135Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T09:33:48.056959Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 4,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , Tensorflow , Deep Learning , scikit learn , git",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T09:43:13.762119Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T09:43:13.792567Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , AWS , DL , Python , Tensorflow",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T09:46:56.307466Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T09:46:56.334842Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS , Tensorflow",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T09:51:53.171068Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T09:51:53.207950Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:07:05.055205Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:07:05.355525Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 0,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:11:06.614859Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:11:06.635522Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:17:35.017816Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:17:35.041502Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL ,AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:30:06.252498Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:30:06.282115Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL ,AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:30:06.252498Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Explain the bias-variance tradeoff in machine learning.",
        "answer": "low bias and high variance lead to overfitting",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:30:58.908214Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Describe a situation where you would choose a decision tree over a linear regression model, and vice versa.",
        "answer": "linear regression for easy data and decision tree for complex data",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:31:35.538913Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "How would you handle imbalanced datasets in a classification problem?",
        "answer": "data augmentation , sampling methods",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:32:05.982539Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "Explain the difference between convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and recurrent neural networks (RNNs).",
        "answer": "CNNs mostly for 2D data , RNN for 1d data",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:32:33.932686Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "What are some common activation functions used in deep learning and why are they important?",
        "answer": "RElu , sigmoid , softmax , decide if neuron activates or not",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:02.991629Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "Describe your experience with different types of regularization techniques in deep learning (e.g., dropout, L1/L2 regularization).",
        "answer": "jhvszSaawe",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:09.315845Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "Explain the concept of backpropagation in the context of training neural networks.",
        "answer": "adhjsfaE",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:12.611375Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "AWS",
        "question": "Compare and contrast EC2, S3, and Lambda.",
        "answer": "AGVFKERFWAkw",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:18.152370Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "AWS",
        "question": "Explain how you would design a highly available and scalable system on AWS.",
        "answer": "DJVSfvawe",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:21.946941Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "AWS",
        "question": "Describe your experience with AWS security best practices (e.g., IAM roles, security groups).",
        "answer": "dj vhAheEBDSVBVV",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:27.078373Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:27.208359Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:27.231849Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL ,AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:30:06.252498Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Explain the bias-variance tradeoff in machine learning.",
        "answer": "low bias and high variance lead to overfitting",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:30:58.908214Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Describe a situation where you would choose a decision tree over a linear regression model, and vice versa.",
        "answer": "linear regression for easy data and decision tree for complex data",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:31:35.538913Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "How would you handle imbalanced datasets in a classification problem?",
        "answer": "data augmentation , sampling methods",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:32:05.982539Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "Explain the difference between convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and recurrent neural networks (RNNs).",
        "answer": "CNNs mostly for 2D data , RNN for 1d data",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:32:33.932686Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "What are some common activation functions used in deep learning and why are they important?",
        "answer": "RElu , sigmoid , softmax , decide if neuron activates or not",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:02.991629Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "Describe your experience with different types of regularization techniques in deep learning (e.g., dropout, L1/L2 regularization).",
        "answer": "jhvszSaawe",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:09.315845Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "DL",
        "question": "Explain the concept of backpropagation in the context of training neural networks.",
        "answer": "adhjsfaE",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:12.611375Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "AWS",
        "question": "Compare and contrast EC2, S3, and Lambda.",
        "answer": "AGVFKERFWAkw",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:18.152370Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "AWS",
        "question": "Explain how you would design a highly available and scalable system on AWS.",
        "answer": "DJVSfvawe",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:21.946941Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "AWS",
        "question": "Describe your experience with AWS security best practices (e.g., IAM roles, security groups).",
        "answer": "dj vhAheEBDSVBVV",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:27.078373Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:37.895327Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:33:37.915767Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "Data Science Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS , SQL",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:06.060899Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:06.101665Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "Data Science Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS , SQL",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:06.060899Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Explain the bias-variance tradeoff in machine learning.",
        "answer": "cdhfabqw",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:26.069498Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:35.593394Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:35.623607Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "Data Science Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS , SQL",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:06.060899Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Explain the bias-variance tradeoff in machine learning.",
        "answer": "cdhfabqw",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:26.069498Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:08.113148Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:08.141326Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 1,
    "desired_position": "Data Science Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "ML , DL , AWS , SQL",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:06.060899Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Explain the bias-variance tradeoff in machine learning.",
        "answer": "cdhfabqw",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T10:57:26.069498Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:10.943403Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:10.957494Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 5,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Delhi",
    "tech_stack": "ML , Scikit Learn , Tensorflow , ANN",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:47.018749Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:47.047912Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 5,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Delhi",
    "tech_stack": "ML , Scikit Learn , Tensorflow , ANN",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T11:05:47.018749Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Explain the bias-variance tradeoff in machine learning.",
        "answer": "bhDFEawf",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T11:06:11.026546Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "Describe different types of machine learning models and provide examples of when each might be appropriate.",
        "answer": "hjsdvkafewawvf",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T11:06:17.672648Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "ML",
        "question": "How would you handle imbalanced datasets in a classification problem?",
        "answer": "DFEEWFAGHHTHDRG",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T11:06:24.202963Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T11:06:35.165035Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T11:06:35.194988Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Tensorflow , Python , AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:10.628940Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:10.662221Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 2,
    "desired_position": "ML Engineer",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Tensorflow , Python , AWS",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:10.628940Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "Tensorflow",
        "question": "Explain the difference between eager execution and graph execution in TensorFlow.",
        "answer": "fjdjsdfjff",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:34.974925Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "Tensorflow",
        "question": "Describe how you would build and train a convolutional neural network (CNN) in TensorFlow for image classification.",
        "answer": "hzsdfadefwwaf",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:41.480888Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:47.783144Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T11:10:47.856899Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 5,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Deep learning , ANN , CNN , AWS , Statistics , Tensorflow , Python",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:00.706907Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:00.739271Z"
  },
  {
    "full_name": "Abdul hadi Zeeshan",
    "experience": 5,
    "desired_position": "ML Intern",
    "location": "Lucknow",
    "tech_stack": "Deep learning , ANN , CNN , AWS , Statistics , Tensorflow , Python",
    "started_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:00.706907Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "tech": "Deep learning",
        "question": "Explain the difference between supervised, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning in the context of deep learning.",
        "answer": "smnaC FEfhwqeFC",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:37.712930Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "Deep learning",
        "question": "Describe a scenario where deep learning is particularly well-suited and another scenario where a different approach might be preferable. Justify your choices.",
        "answer": "[SKIPPED]",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:45.832651Z"
      },
      {
        "tech": "Deep learning",
        "question": "What are some common challenges encountered when training deep learning models, and how can these be addressed?",
        "answer": "[SKIPPED]",
        "answered_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:48.730296Z"
      }
    ],
    "completed_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:55.927936Z",
    "email_hash": "707ac81077795c9e242f4611568d6d7cf327a3ea1044431a93834c5108063317",
    "phone_hash": "ae3fb5d7420aa91162a2ffecb9103d6ffd095cbba9e73eaf8fca75cde5daedb9",
    "saved_at": "2025-08-10T12:49:55.957089Z"
  }
]